(Howard:)-Oh, God, this is good.
-Let me ask you a question.
(Raj:)Do you believe you're going to go to hell
for eating sweet-and-sour pork?
(Howard:)Jews don't have hell.
We have acid reflux.
(Leonard:)Do you want the last dumpling, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Certainly. It's not like I have
to moderate my food intake...
(Sheldon:)...because I'm planning on eating again
very shortly.
(Sheldon:)Mm, mm, mm.
So you wanna do something tonight?
No, I can't. I gotta pick up my mom
from her water-aerobics class.
Eighteen overweight women
flapping their arm fat...
(Howard:)...in a swimming pool.
It's like the manatee tank
at SeaWorld.
(Leonard:)-What about you, Raj?
-Oh, there it is.
Now you don't have a girlfriend
you wanna hang out with me again.
(Leonard:)I never stopped hanging out with you.